So, what's the big news you had us rush all the way over here for?
是什麼天驚地動的大消息 要我們馬上趕過來？
It took you 45 minutes to cross a street.
你們光過個馬路就花了四十五分鐘
Come on, guys. It's just one baby.
真是的，只不過是個嬰兒
Oh, sure, now you guys clam up.
好吧，你們現在都沒有人要幫腔
Our news. My company has asked me to head up our office in Tulsa.
我們要宣佈的消息就是 公司要我去土爾沙帶領新的分公司
So as of Monday, I'm being officially relocated.
所以從星期一開始 我已經正式被調職了
- Oh, my God! - What? Monday?
-喔，我的天！ -什麼？星期一？
- How long do you have to go for? - They said it could be up to a year.
-你得要去多久呢？ -他們說有可能會長達一年
- A year? - Well, do you have to go?
-一年？ -那你也要去嗎？
Well, I kind of have to, don't I?
我似乎是沒有選擇，不是嗎？
Because of this stupid thing.
都是因為這個愚蠢的東西
There's nothing like the support of your loving wife, huh?
再也沒有比愛妻的支持 更棒的東西了
Wait a minute. Wait, you can't go to Tulsa.
等一下，你不能去土爾沙
Maybe you forgot, but we have tickets to the Jets game next week!
也許你忘了 但是下星期我們要去看球賽的！
I'm sorry, but I don't think I'll be able to make it.
我很抱歉，但是我想我可能去不了
But we were gonna go see the Jets!
但是我們是要去看球賽耶！
You can't go. I mean, you're the glue that holds this group together.
你不能離開我們 你就像是維繫這個圈子的靈魂人物
- Really? - Not you.
-真的嗎？ -不是你
This whole thing is gonna be okay.
一切都會沒問題的
They said they'd rent us a house in the suburbs. You guys can come and visit.
他們會幫我們在郊區租房子 你們可以過來看我們
Oh, God, that is so not gonna happen.
喔，天啊，那真的是不太可能
I can't believe you guys are moving.
我真不敢相信你們要搬走了
- I call their apartment! - No!
-我承接他們的公寓！ -不行！
The One With The Pediatrician
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
- Here you go, Rach. - Thank you, Joey.
-咖啡來了，瑞秋 -謝謝你，喬伊
You know what? I'm not even sure I can have caffeine.
你知道嗎？ 我不確定可不可以喝有咖啡因的東西
I went through this with Ben and Carol. One coffee won't affect your milk.
我養育班還有凱蘿的經驗告訴我 一杯咖啡不會影響你的母乳的
Just to be sure, I'm gonna call Dr. Wiener.
為了安全起見 我要打電話給歪愣醫師
Every time?
這麼好笑嗎？
You don't have to call him whenever you have a question, okay?
沒有必要每次有問題 都打電話給他，好嗎？
- Trust me. I know this. - All right. I trust you.
-相信我，我是有經驗的 -好吧，我相信你
I can see you dialing. I don't understand why..
我看到你在撥電話 我不瞭解為什麼…
I'm on the phone! Dr. Wiener?
我在講電話！歪愣醫師嗎？
It's so weird seeing Ross and Rachel with a baby. It's just so grownup.
看到羅斯跟瑞秋有了小孩 真是奇怪，好像大人
I know, yeah. I feel like we're all growing up.
我知道，是啊
覺得好像我們都一起長大了
A person named "Wiener." God, that kills me.
有人的名字叫「歪愣」 真是笑死我了
- Look at you all grownup. - Well, actually, you know what?
-瞧瞧你就像個大人 -事實上，你知道嗎？
I am, you know?
我的確是長大了，知道嗎？
Well, that whole thing with Rachel made me realize..
跟瑞秋發生的那件事讓我意識到…
that maybe I'm ready for a more serious relationship, you know?
或許我已經準備好 要接受更認真的交往了
Like, I'd like to meet a nice, mature, commitment-minded lady.
我想要找一個 善良、成熟、穩重的女孩子
And looks aren't as important as..
外表並不是非常…
Nah, she's gotta be hot.
不，她一定要很辣才行
You know, I might know somebody.
我也許認識這樣的人
How about you set me up with someone, and we double-date?
要不要你幫我找個對象 然後我們一起兩對約會
I can do that. Yeah. How's Friday?
我可以啊，星期五怎樣呢？
- Done! - All right.
-沒問題！ -好的
Good, really? Okay, let's see.
很好，真的？ 好，我們來看看
All right.
好的
You know who's great? Sandy Poopack.
你知道誰不錯嗎？珊蒂普霸
"Poopack"?
「普霸」？
Yeah. All right. Well, that rules out Lana Titwyler.
好吧，沒關係 那萊娜緹婉樂可能也不行了
- I've got good news. - You got out of the whole Tulsa thing?
-我有好消息 -你不用去土爾沙了嗎？
Okay, I have news.
好吧，我有新消息
You don't have to move to Tulsa. You can stay here and keep your job.
你不用跟我一起搬到土爾沙 你可以待在這裡，保有工作
That's great! How?
太好了！怎麼回事？
My boss and I worked out a deal where I'm in Tulsa four days a week.
老闆跟我達成一個協議 我一星期在土爾沙待四天就可以了
So the other three, I can be here with you.
所以另外三天我可以跟你在一起
So you're gonna be gone four days a week?
所以一星期有四天你不在？
No.
不行
I'm sorry, are you just used to saying that?
不好意思，你是不是 太習慣說不行了呢？
No. I can't be away from you for that long.
不是，我不能跟你分開那麼久的
- Really? - Yeah, you're my husband.
-真的嗎？ -是啊，你是我先生
I won't live in a different state than you for 208 days out of the year.
我不要一年兩百零八天跟你住在不同州
That's fast math. We could use you in Tulsa.
算的真快，我們土爾沙的分公司 可以聘請你的
Thanks for trying to figure out a way, but if you go to Tulsa, I go with you.
謝謝你試著想出更好的方式 但是如果你要去土爾沙，我會跟你去
You said that without gagging.
你這樣說的時候竟然沒有做嘔吐狀
I know!
真的耶！
Well, excuse me?
你說什麼？
Oh, yeah? Well, up yours too!
喔？那你也去吃屎吧！
- Who the hell was that? - Dr. Wiener.
-那到底是誰啊？ -歪愣醫師
Rach, you can't call people at 3:00 in the morning.
瑞秋，你不能在凌晨三點 打電話給人家的
You know what? You sound just like his wife.
你知道嗎？ 你聽起來就像他老婆一樣
Was there anything even wrong with Emma?
艾□有怎樣嗎？
Yes, of course there is! Okay? I'm not insane.
當然是有怎樣！ 好嗎？我又不是瘋了
What was it?
是怎樣？
Hiccups.
打嗝
I told you, you can't call him every time any little thing comes up.
我告訴過你了，不能每次 有雞毛蒜皮小事都打電話給他
Well, not anymore I can't. He fired us!
看來我是真的不能了 他不接我們了！
Can you believe that?
你敢相信嗎？
I could believe it if he came here and hit you over the head with a copy of Highlights.
我敢相信如果他在這裡 一定會用雜誌砸你的頭
What are we gonna do? We have to find a pediatrician.
我們該怎麼辦呢？ 我們得再另找一個小兒科醫師了
Wait, Monica said that when you guys were growing up..
等一下，摩妮卡說你們小時候…
you liked your doctor. What was his name?
很喜歡你們的醫師 他叫什麼名字呢？
Dr. Gettleman?
葛曼醫師嗎？
Yeah, no, I don't think that's a good idea.
不，我認為這不是個好主意
In fact, I think he's dead.
事實上，我想他死了
Why does everything happen to me?
為什麼壞事都發生在我身上？
I promise, first thing tomorrow, we'll find another doctor.
我保證，明天第一件事 就是找到一個新的醫生
But I gotta get up early, and I'm not feeling well.
但是我要很早起床 而且我現在覺得不是很舒服
You're not feeling well? What do you have? Rubella?
你不舒服？ 是怎麼回事呢？德國麻疹嗎？
Because don't go near Emma, she has not had that shot.
別靠近艾□ 她還沒有注射預防針
You know, come to think of it, it does feel rubella-like.
我仔細想想 倒還感覺像是德國麻疹
Wiener!
歪愣！
Wiener! Wiener! Wiener!
歪愣！歪愣！歪愣！
Rachel!
瑞秋！
Great! Now he's gonna know it was me!
太棒了，現在他就知道那是我了！
And the kung pao chicken.
還有宮保雞丁
Utensils and plates for one.
一人用的餐具
And can you read the order back to me?
可以重複我的訂單嗎？
Great.
太棒了
Yeah. Okay, thanks. Bye.
好的，謝謝，再見
So how is this for our big double date tonight?
看我為今晚我們兩對約會打扮如何？
Oh, my God.
喔，天啊
Great. Just the reaction I was hoping for.
太棒了，這正是我要的反應
Yeah, so you found someone for me? You didn't forget?
是啊，你有幫我找到人嗎？ 你沒有忘記吧？
Of course not. And you'll love Mary Ellen.
當然沒有 你會愛死□莉艾倫的
She's really smart and cute and funny and..
她真的很聰明、可愛風趣，而且…
I can't tell you how I know this, but she is not opposed to threesomes.
我不能告訴你我是怎麼知道的 但是她並不反對三人行
All right.
好耶
- So tell me something about my guy. - No.
-說一點我的約會對象吧 -不行
Come on, give me something. What's his name?
別這樣，透露一點嘛 他叫什麼名字？
I'm not sure I understand the question.
我不明白你的問題
What do they call him?
大家都是怎麼叫他的？
- Mike. - Mike. Okay, what's his last name?
-麥克 -麥克，好的，他姓什麼呢？
Damn it! Is there no mystery left in romance anymore?!
可惡！就不能為浪漫 而保有神秘感嗎？
We'll see you and Mike at the restaurant in a couple hours.
幾個小時之後在餐廳 與你跟麥克見
All right, great. See you. Bye-bye.
好的，沒問題 待會見，拜拜
Why'd I have to say Mike? I don't know a Mike! Why couldn't I have said..?
我為什麼要說麥克呢？根本不認識 誰叫麥克的！為什麼不說…？
There's no guys in there!
這裡面根本就沒有男生！
So this is being a parent, huh?
所以這就是帶孩子，是吧？
I think I can handle this.
我想我可以處理得很好的
Too intense. Too intense.
太難了，太難了
Well, I did it.
好了，我說了
I told my crew at the restaurant I'm heading off to Tulsa.
我告訴餐廳的班底 我要搬到土爾沙了
- Oh, yeah? How'd they take it. - Pretty well. Yeah.
-是嗎？他們反應如何？ -還不錯
They were brave little soldiers.
他們是勇敢的小尖兵
Did their best to be stoic.
盡全力冷靜
Some of them even high-fived each other to mask their pain.
有些還互相擊掌來掩飾離別的傷痛
It's impossible to find a good doctor. How do you know the good ones..
要找好醫生真是好難 要如何分辨哪個是好醫生…
from the ones who'll push their penis against your knee?
哪個又會拿小弟弟 摩擦你的膝蓋呢？
Excuse me?
什麼？
I know what she's talking about.
我知道她的意思
You probably also had the piano teacher with the wandering hands.
你們或許也碰過 會毛手毛腳的鋼琴老師吧
Well, we've gotta find a new pediatrician.
我們要找新的小兒科醫生
Ross was getting sick last night, and Emma may have caught it.
羅斯昨晚不舒服 艾□或許也被感染到了
- Why don't you see Dr. Gettleman? - Ross said he died.
-你為什麼不去找葛曼醫生呢？ -羅斯說他死了
He didn't die. I just saw his daughter last week.
他沒死 我上星期才遇到他女兒
She said he was fine. Her, on the other hand, botched Botox.
她說他很好，但是她呢 可被肉毒桿菌搞慘了
Great. Well then, I'm gonna take Emma to see him.
太好了，那我要帶艾□去找他
I wonder why Ross said that he died?
為什麼羅斯說他死了呢？
Maybe he confused him with his childhood therapist.
或許他把他跟 他小時候的心理醫生搞混了
He saw a therapist?
他有心理醫生？
He used to have a recurring nightmare. It freaked him out.
他以前常常做重複的噩夢 嚇死他了
Wow, what was it?
哇，什麼噩夢呢？
That I was going to eat him.
夢到我要吃掉他
Mike!
麥克！
Yeah?
怎樣？
Okay.
好了
I can't believe I'm doing this with you.
真不敢相信，我竟然跟你做這件事
Although I did just end a nine-year relationship..
我才剛結束一段九年的戀情…
so I should be open to taking some risks.
所以我應該敞開心胸迎接一些挑戰
That's good. Get all that boring stuff out now.
這樣很好 把那些無聊的舊東西拋掉
Everything is gonna be fine. Follow my lead, okay?
一切安啦 跟著我就沒事，好嗎？
All you have to do is pretend to be Mike.
你只要假裝是麥克就可以了
- I am Mike. - Attaboy.
-我就是麥克啊 -演的真不錯
Here they come.
她們來了
- I'm Phoebe. - Phoebe. Mike. How you doing?
-我是菲比 -菲比，這位是麥克，你好嗎？
- Nice to meet you. - Joey, this is Mary Ellen Jenkins.
-很高興認識你 -喬伊，這位是□莉艾倫珍金
So, Mike, how do you and Joey know each other, anyway?
麥克，你跟喬伊是怎麼認識的呢？
How do Joey and I know each other?
我跟喬伊是怎麼認識的呢？
If I had a nickel for every time somebody's asked me that.
如果每次有人問我這問題 我就有五塊錢賺，那我就變富翁了
- From school. - We met in college.
-在學校認識的 -我們在大學認識的
I mean high school.
我是說高中
You guys go way back, then. So, what are you up to these days?
那你們認識可久了 那你現在是做什麼的呢？
- Well, I'm a lawyer. - Mike, attorney at law!
-我是律師 -麥克，律師！
- Actually, I just gave up my practice. - What?
-事實上，我才剛放棄執業 -什麼？
That's the kind of thing you usually run by me.
這種事你應該先跟我討論的
I want to play piano professionally. If I don't do this now, I never will.
我想要成為專業鋼琴音樂家 如果現在不趕快做，就來不及了
Great. I like that better than the lawyer thing.
太好了，我喜歡音樂家勝過律師
Which is why I waited until now to introduce you to Mike.
這就是為什麼我等到現在 才介紹麥克給你
You thought he was still a lawyer.
你不是還以為他是律師嗎？
No, that's not what I meant. Let's get you a cocktail.
不，我並沒有那樣說 我們幫你點杯雞尾酒吧
What are you doing?
你在做什麼呢？
Looking for restaurant jobs for you in Tulsa.
幫你在土爾沙找餐廳的工作
That's so sweet. Did you find anything?
真是窩心，有找到嗎？
- Slim Pickins. - Nothing, huh?
-速食外餐 -什麼都沒有，是吧？
No. Slim Pickins. It's a barbecue joint.
不，速食外餐，是間烤肉店
They're looking for a cook. Actually, "cook" may be a bit of a stretch.
他們在找廚師，事實上 並不全然是「廚師」
They're looking for somebody to shovel mesquite.
他們在找炒豆子的幫手
"Slim Pickins"? That is so cheesy.
「速食外餐」？聽起來真是不高級
Well, So Cheesy also has an opening.
「布高吉」也有在徵人
Honey, that's okay. I know this woman, Nancy..
親愛的，沒關係 我認識一個叫南西的人…
who's a restaurant biz headhunter. She may know something.
她是專門幫餐廳獵人頭的 她或許會知道一些職缺
Can I say how much I appreciate you coming with me?
我真的是太感激你願意跟我去
When we get to Tulsa, I am taking you for a great dinner at Slim Pickins.
當我們抵達土爾沙 我會帶你去速食外餐吃大餐的
So Cheesy?
那布高吉呢？
Whole Hog?
全豬餐廳呢？
It's gonna be tough to keep kosher in Tulsa.
在土爾沙要找到正式餐廳還真是不簡單
Hi, Nancy? Hi, it's Monica Geller.
嗨，南西嗎？ 嗨，我是摩妮卡蓋勒
I'm good. Listen, I'm looking for a job in Tulsa.
我很好，我需要在土爾沙找份工作
Yeah, well, my husband's been relocated.
是啊，因為我先生被調職到那邊
Because I love him.
因為我愛他
No, I don't want a job in New York.
不，我不想要紐約的工作
Javu's looking? Oh, my God!
傑屋在找人？喔，我的天啊！
He asked for me personally? Oh, my God!
他特別指名要我？ 喔，我的天啊！
Wow, this is really, really flattering.
哇，我真的是太受寵若驚了
But I'm moving to Tulsa.
但是我要搬到土爾沙了
So, just, if you would tell Javu..
所以，請你告訴傑屋…
I'll take it!
我接受這份工作！
My name's Rachel Greene. I have an appointment for Emma.
我是瑞秋葛林 我有幫艾□預約看診
Dr. Gettleman is finishing up with a patient. He'll be out shortly.
葛曼醫生快看完病人了 他等一下就會出來
I think you just have a cold. It's definitely not strep.
我想你只是感冒了 沒有什麼嚴重性
Thanks, doctor.
謝了，醫生
- Would you like a lollipop? - Do you even have to ask?
-要不要來根棒棒糖呢？ -還用問嗎？
He is alive!
他還活著！
It's so surprising that you and Joey have known each other for so long..
好奇怪，你跟喬伊認識這麼久了…
and I've never heard about you.
而我卻從沒有聽說過你
That's because we had a bit of a falling out.
因為我們有吵過架
Mike hit my mom with a car.
麥克開車撞到我媽
- No, I didn't. - That's okay. I have forgiven you.
-才沒，我沒有 -沒關係，我已經原諒你了
Now we're friends again, and everything's great.
現在我們又是朋友了 一切都很美好
Well, wait. Is your mom okay?
等一下，你媽還好吧？
Please, we're trying to have a conversation.
拜託，我們在講話耶
You're a lot nicer on Days of Our Lives.
你在《我們的日子》中親切多了
Days of Our Lives! That's why you look so familiar!
《我們的日子》！ 怪不得你看起來有點眼熟！
- What? - What?
-什麼？ -什麼？
What?
什麼？
Do you not know each other?
你們彼此不認識嗎？
Of course we do. He's playing a game we used to play in high school.
我們當然認識 他是在玩我們高中常玩的遊戲
We pretend we don't know each other. We played all kinds of games.
我們假裝不認識 我們玩很多種遊戲的
You remember that one where I punch you in the face for not being cool?
你還記得有一次 你因為太蠢而被我揍嗎？
Let me ask you something: How many sisters does Joey have?
讓我問你一個問題 喬伊有幾個姐妹呢？
- Six. - No, he doesn't. He has seven.
-六個 -不，他有七個
What are you doing? I said seven!
你在搞什麼鬼？我比了七個！
Joey, why did you set me up with a stranger?
喬伊，為什麼你要介紹陌生人給我呢？
Because I forgot about our date. I'm so sorry.
因為我忘記了，我很抱歉
I'm sorry too. And just to be clear, I didn't hit his mother with a car.
我也很抱歉，還有要澄清一下 我沒有開車撞他媽
Although I'd like to be hit by one right now.
不過我現在真的很想被車撞一下
Yeah, no problem.
是喔，沒問題
You are unbelievable. I spent so much time finding the perfect girl for you.
你真是太不應該了 我花這麼多時間幫你找完美的對象
Mary Ellen is really smart and cute and loose.
□莉艾倫真的很聰明 很可愛又很隨便
嘿！
Who are you kidding?
你別裝了吧？
You find some guy off the street for me?
你在街上隨便捉個男的塞給我？
God, this is humiliating!
天啊，這真是太羞辱人了！
I'm so sorry. If you don't like this guy, I can find you a better one.
我很抱歉，如果你不喜歡這一個 我可以幫你找更好的
Mike? Mike?
麥克？麥克？
I'm out of here.
我要走了
It was nice meeting you.
很高興認識你
- You're leaving too? - I'll stay if you can tell me my name.
-你也要走？ -你說的出我的名字，我就留下
Have a good night.
再見
We leave tomorrow, and you still have a lot to pack.
我們明天就要走了 而你還有好多東西要打包
You're right.
你說得對
Maybe I shouldn't go.
或許我不應該去
What?
什麼？
So Nancy told me about this job at this great restaurant, Javu?
南西告訴我有一個 很棒的餐廳在徵人，傑屋？
But it's just a little outside of Tulsa.
離土爾沙不會太遠
Well, how far outside?
那是多遠呢？
Manhattan?
曼哈頓遠嗎？
And you're thinking of taking it?
你要接受這份工作嗎？
Before, you said that being with me was more important than any job.
你之前說跟我在一起 比任何工作都重要
But I guess now it's old job, me, new job.
但我猜，現在是 舊工作，我，新工作
I'm gonna miss this hand!
我會想念這隻手的！
I know this is a lot to ask..
我知道這很過份…
but, my God, this is a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity.
但是，天啊，這是千載難逢的好機會
What happened to "you can't live without me four days a week"?
那你說無法忍受每星期四天 要分開，是怎麼回事呢？
Well, if you really think about it, I mean, four days is not that long.
如果你仔細想想 四天並不是很長的時間
I see you Monday before you go to work..
星期一你去上班前我會見到你…
and Thursday when you get back..
然後星期四晚上我也會見到你…
and I always work late on Tuesdays, so really if you think about it..
而我總是在星期二忙得很晚 所以如果你仔細想想…
it's really just one day.
事實上只有分開一天而已
And well, if we can't make it one day, we got real problems, my friend.
而如果我們連一天都撐不住 我們真的是有大問題了
- I think you should take the job. - Really?
-我認為你應該接受這份工作 -真的嗎？
I know it must be important to you when you start chattering like a monkey.
當你開始像猴子一樣鬼吼時 我就知道這對你一定很重要
That's the nicest thing anybody's ever said to me.
這是我聽過最美好的形容了
It's your dream job. I can't make you pass it up.
這是你的夢想工作 我不能要求你放棄的
Besides, I'm proud of you.
況且我還以你為榮
- You are? - Yeah.
-真的嗎？ -是啊
And when I get to Tulsa and people say, "Where's the missus"..
當我去到土爾沙，有人問我 「你老婆呢？」
I'll tell them she's a chef at Javu.
我會告訴他們，她在傑屋當主廚
And then, when they stare at me blankly..
然後，當他們 搞不清狀況盯著我看時…
I'll make some offensive Tulsa joke, and thus, begin my isolation.
我就會說一些污辱土爾沙的笑話 然後開始被他們排擠
- How was the pediatrician? - I really liked him.
-新醫生怎樣呢？ -我真的很喜歡他
Yeah, yeah. It was really, really, really good.
是啊，是啊 真的，真的，真的很不錯
- You promised not to say anything. - I know.
-你答應我不會說出去的 -我知道
Ross still sees his pediatrician!
羅斯還在看他小時候的醫生！
I don't care.
我不在乎
Are you serious? You still see Dr. Gettleman?
真的嗎？ 你還在看葛曼醫師？
He is a brilliant diagnostician!
他是醫術高明的診斷師！
Diagnostician or boo-boo fixer?
診斷師還是醫生叔叔呢？
Seriously, you gotta go to an appropriate doctor.
真的，你應該去看適合你的醫生才對
And not an orthodontist..
不是牙科醫生…
not a gynecologist..
不是婦科醫生…
and not a veterinarian..
也更不是獸醫
Why? I know it's a little weird, but he is a great doctor, okay?
為什麼？我知道這是有點怪 但是他是個很棒的醫生，好嗎？
He knows my medical history.
他知道我的病史
And every time I go in there, he makes a big deal.
而且每次我去看病 他都非常的慎重其事
You know, "Look, it's my favorite patient."
你知道的 「瞧，這是我最喜歡的病人」
Does he say that before he sticks his thermometer in your tushy?
是不是在把體溫計 插到你嘴裡之前說的呢？
I seem to remember someone bringing his security blanket to college.
我還記得有人把他的 安全毛毯帶到大學宿舍
That was not a security blanket. That was a wall hanging.
那不是安全毛毯 那是壁毯
It didn't spend much time on the wall!
它倒是沒有被掛在牆上太久！
Excuse me.
對不起
Hi. I was hoping to run into you. Can we talk?
嗨，我原本就希望可以再遇到你 我們可以談談嗎？
Sure.
當然
Yeah. There's someone I want you to meet.
我想要介紹你認識一個人
This is my best friend from high school.
這位是我高中最要好的朋友
I'm sorry, I don't think I know you.
很抱歉，我並不認識你
How hard was that?
真是太容易了
Look, I'm sorry, really. I'm so embarrassed.
我真的很抱歉 我實在太不好意思了
Please.
拜託
Really, I'm a pretty nice guy. Just ask my parole officer.
真的，我是個還不錯的人 你可以問我的保釋官
Apparently, I'm not a funny guy.
很明顯地，我並不是很風趣
Well, why did you go along with that?
那你為什麼要這樣做呢？
Because I was told that I'd get a free dinner, which I didn't.
因為他說，我可以吃一頓 免費的晚餐，不過並沒有
And that I'd meet a pretty girl, which I did.
還有他說，我可以認識 漂亮的女生，這倒是有
That's true.
那倒是真的
Well, is anything you told me about yourself true?
那你告訴我的事有哪些是真的呢？
My name is Mike. And I do play piano.
我的名字真的是麥克 還有我真的會彈鋼琴
- Prove it. - There isn't a piano here.
-證明給我看 -這裡並沒有鋼琴
That wouldn't stand in the way of a true pianist.
那對真正的鋼琴家不會是問題吧
Okay.
好吧
You are really good.
你真的很棒
- I play a little guitar myself. - Really? That's great.
-我會彈一點吉他 -真的？太棒了
- What kind of music do you play? - Like acoustic, folksy stuff, you know?
-你彈奏什麼種音樂呢？ -像是重原音、有民俗風味的
But right now I'm working on a couple lron Maiden covers.
但是我現在在製作CD封面
Do you think that, maybe, sometime, I could..
你想，或許，有空的話，我可…
It's okay. Go ahead, ask me out.
沒關係的，來吧，約我吧
Okay. You think, maybe, sometime I could take you out?
好吧，你想，或許有空的話 我可以約你出去嗎？
You just caught me off guard.
你真是讓我一點心理準備都沒有
Yeah, that would be nice.
好啊，我很樂意
Look at this! My two best friends!
瞧瞧！我兩個最要好的朋友！
Excuse me. I don't mean to be a jerk..
不好意思，我不想要太機車…
but the baby with the rash came in after me.
但是那個長疹子的嬰兒 是在我後面進來的
- The doctor will be right with you, sir. - I hear you..
-醫生等一下就可以看你了，先生 -我知道…
but do you have any harder puzzles?
但是你有沒有比較高難度的謎題呢？
Mommy, I can't find Waldo.
媽咪，我找不到華多
What page are you on?
你在第幾頁呢？
What, the circus? He's behind the elephant.
遊樂場嗎？他在大象後面
Wow. So your child's a big fan of the Waldo books too?
哇，你的孩子一定也很迷華多
Yeah, that's how I know.
是啊，所以我也很熟
- I'm Ross, by the way. - Hi, I'm Sally.
-對了，我叫羅斯 -嗨，我叫莎莉
So no ring. Can I assume you're also a single parent?
沒有戒指，所以我推想你也是單親？
- I am a single parent. - It's hard, isn't it?
-我是單親沒錯 -很難，對吧？
There's no time for a social life. Where are you gonna meet someone?
根本沒有可以社交的時間 要去哪裡認識朋友呢？
- Well.. - Mommy, I can't..
-那個… -媽咪，我找不…
Sea shore? Row boat.
海邊嗎？在小船上
Let's say, I don't know, you met someone in the pediatrician's office.
我想，我不知道 可以在小兒科醫生那裡認識人吧
Rossie? We're ready for you.
小羅斯？輪到你了
Yeah..
是啊…
Come on, Ross Jr. It's time to go in.
走吧，小羅斯 輪到我們了
Mommy.
媽咪
Mommy, what's wrong with that man?
媽咪，那個人是怎麼了？
Hey, I helped you find Waldo!
嘿，是我幫你找到華多的耶！
- Good, you haven't left yet. - Where have you been?
-太好了，你還沒走 -你去哪了？
I got held up at Dr. Gettleman's office.
有事情在葛曼醫師那耽擱了一下
There was some guy that freaked everybody out.
有一個人嚇壞了所有的人
I don't think I'm going back there.
我想我再也不要回去那裡了
You got here just in time. I really have to go, buddy.
你正好趕上 我得要走了，兄弟
Oh, man.
喔，真是的
- Promise to call me when you land? - Of course I will. I love you.
-答應我一下飛機就打電話 -當然，我愛你
I love you too.
我也愛你
Watch the tongue, people. We got a baby over here.
不要舌吻，你們，兒童不宜
- Bye, Chandler. - Bye.
-再見，錢德 -再見
- Bye, honey. - Bye.
-再見，親愛的 -再見
- What's the matter, Joe? - I'm mad at you for leaving.
-怎麼了，喬伊？ -我很生氣你要走
You know, you're nothing but a big leaver.
你知道嗎？你什麼都不會 就最會拋棄人家
A big leaver with a stupid suitcase.
帶著笨行李的負心漢
Any chance you're trying to pick a fight to make all of this easier?
你是不是故意說一些氣話 讓自己好過點呢？
Dude, you see right through me!
老兄，你真是太瞭解我了！
Okay, well.. Bye, Mon.
好了，那麼…再見了，摩妮卡
Bye, Ross. Rachel.
再見，羅斯，瑞秋
- Bye, Emma. - Okay, bye-bye.
-再見，艾□ -好了，拜拜
Have a good trip. Okay. Oh, my God.
旅途愉快，好了，喔，天啊
Wait.
錢德，等一下
It goes old job..
應該是舊工作…
new job..
新工作…
and you.
然後是你
This is just something I have to do.
那只不過是我要做的工作
I know.
我知道
I love you so much.
我好愛你
I know that too.
我也知道
Don't worry. I'll be back before you know it.
別擔心 我很快就會回來了
Yes, it will be the same.
是的，一切都不會變
Because I know, that's how.
因為我就是知道
I promise.
我保證
You double promise?
你可以雙重保證嗎？
Call me when you land.
一下機就打電話給我
- Can I talk now? - Okay, bye.
-輪到我講了嗎？ -好的，再見
- Joey! - He had to board.
-喬伊！ -他要登機了